So, let's do this calculation a bit more in detail.
下面我们进行详细的计算
Since we have eight emails in total,
我们共有 8 封邮件
and three of them are spam and five of them are non-spam,
3 封是垃圾邮件 5 封是非垃圾邮件
or ham, than our prior probabilities are
所以我们的先验概率为
three over eight for spam and five over eight for ham.
垃圾邮件 八分之三 非垃圾邮件 八分之五
So, on to calculate the posteriors.
我们继续算后验概率
Say we have a spam email.
假如现在有一封垃圾邮件
Since there are three of them,
因为三封垃圾邮件中
and one contains the word easy and two don't,
一封含有 “easy” 两封没有
then the probability for containing the word easy is one-third and
所以这封垃圾邮件含有 “easy” 的概率是三分之一
for not containing it is two-thirds, if you're spam.
不含 “easy” 的概率是三分之二
And as we've calculated before,
跟我们之前计算的一样
the probability of containing the word easy,
非垃圾邮件含有 “easy” 的概率
if you're ham, is one-fifth,
是五分之一
and of not containing,
不含 “easy” 的概率
if you're ham, is four-fifths.
是五分之四
Now, by the rule of conditional probabilities,
根据条件概率
the probability that an email is spam and contains
一封邮件是垃圾邮件 并且它包含 “easy” 的概率
the word easy is the product of these two,
是两个事件的乘积
three over eight times one third, which is one-eighth.
八分之三乘以三分之一 即八分之一
In a similar way, we calculated the probability of being
同样 我们计算一下
spam and not containing the word easy, which is one-fourth,
一封邮件是垃圾邮件 但它不包含 “easy” 的概率 即四分之一
and the probabilities of being ham and containing the word easy is one-eighth,
非垃圾邮件包含 “easy” 的概率是八分之一
and not containing it is one-half.
非垃圾邮件不包含 “easy” 的概率是二分之一
Now, this is where we apply Bayes rule.
在这里使用贝叶斯定理
We know that the email contains the word easy,
我们知道这封邮件中包含 “easy”
so our entire universe consists of only these two two cases,
所以我们只考虑两种情况
when the email is spam or ham.
邮件是垃圾邮件还是非垃圾邮件
Those two have the same probability, one-eighth, of happening.
这两种情况发生的概率相同 都是八分之一
So, once we normalize the probabilities,
我们把这两个概率归一化
they both turn into 50 percent,
它们都是 50%
thus our two posterior probabilities are 50 percent.
所以我们的后验概率都是 50%
For ham emails, we can do the same procedure.
对非垃圾邮件 可以采取同样的流程
Our priors are three over eight and five over eight, as before.
我们的先验概率分别是八分之三和八分之五
Our probabilities of containing the word money,
包含 “money” 的概率
and not containing it,
和不包含 “money” 的概率
are two-thirds and one-third for the spam emails,
垃圾邮件 分别是三分之二和三分之一
and one-fifth and four-fifths for the ham emails.
而非垃圾邮件 分别是五分之一和五分之四
Our products of probabilities are then one-quarter,
乘积分别是四分之一
one-quarter, one-eighth, and one-half.
四分之一 八分之一 二分之一
But since the email contains the word money,
由于邮件中包含 “money”
then we only care about these two.
所以我们只考虑两种情况
Since one-fourth is twice as much as one-eighth,
由于四分之一是八分之一的两倍
when we normalize them we get two-thirds,
我们在归一化处理时 垃圾邮件的概率是三分之二
or 66.7% for spam,
即 66.7%
and one-third, or 33.3% for ham.
非垃圾邮件的概率是三分之一 即 33.3%
These are the posteriors.
这就是后验概率